2.3.10.1   L1    Ensure 'Network access: Allow anonymous SID/Name translation... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.10.2   L1    ... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.10.3   L1    ... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.10.4   L2    Ensure 'Network access: Do not allow storage of passwords an... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.10.5   L1    Ensure 'Network access: Let Everyone permissions apply to an... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.10.6   L1    Configure 'Network access: Named Pipes that can be accessed ... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.10.8   L1    Configure 'Network access: Remotely accessible registry path... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.10.9   L1    Configure 'Network access: Remotely accessible registry path... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.10.10  L1    Ensure 'Network access: Restrict anonymous access to Named P... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.10.11  L1    ... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.10.12  L1    Ensure 'Network access: Shares that can be accessed anonymou... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.10.13  L1    Ensure 'Network access: Sharing and security model for local... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.11.1   L1    Ensure 'Network security: Allow Local System to use computer... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.11.2   L1    Ensure 'Network security: Allow LocalSystem NULL session fal... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.11.3   L1    Ensure 'Network Security: Allow PKU2U authentication request... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.11.4   L1    Ensure 'Network security: Configure encryption types allowed... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.11.5   L1    Ensure 'Network security: Do not store LAN Manager hash valu... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.11.6   L1    Ensure 'Network security: Force logoff when logon hours expi... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.11.7   L1    Ensure 'Network security: LAN Manager authentication level' ... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.11.8   L1    Ensure 'Network security: LDAP client signing requirements' ... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.11.9   L1    Ensure 'Network security: Minimum session security for NTLM ... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.11.10  L1    Ensure 'Network security: Minimum session security for NTLM ... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.13.1   L1    Ensure 'Shutdown: Allow system to be shut down without havin... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.15.1   L1    Ensure 'System objects: Require case insensitivity for non-W... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.15.2   L1    Ensure 'System objects: Strengthen default permissions of in... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.17.1   L1    Ensure 'User Account Control: Admin Approval Mode for the Bu... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.17.2   L1    Ensure 'User Account Control: Behavior of the elevation prom... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.17.3   L1    Ensure 'User Account Control: Behavior of the elevation prom... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.17.4   L1    Ensure 'User Account Control: Detect application installatio... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.17.5   L1    Ensure 'User Account Control: Only elevate UIAccess applicat... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.17.6   L1    Ensure 'User Account Control: Run all administrators in Admi... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.17.7   L1    Ensure 'User Account Control: Switch to the secure desktop w... Group Policy Settings     True        
2.3.17.8   L1    Ensure 'User Account Control: Virtualize file and registry w... Group Policy Settings     True        
5.1        L1    Ensure 'Print Spooler (Spooler)' is set to 'Disabled' (DC only) Group Policy Settings     True        
9.1.1      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Domain: Firewall state' is set to ... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.1.2      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Domain: Inbound connections' is se... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.1.3      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Domain: Outbound connections' is s... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.1.4      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Domain: Settings: Display a notifi... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.1.5      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Domain: Logging: Name' is set to '... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.1.6      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Domain: Logging: Size limit (KB)' ... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.1.7      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Domain: Logging: Log dropped packe... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.1.8      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Domain: Logging: Log successful co... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.2.1      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Private: Firewall state' is set to... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.2.2      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Private: Inbound connections' is s... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.2.3      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Private: Outbound connections' is ... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.2.4      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Private: Settings: Display a notif... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.2.5      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Private: Logging: Name' is set to ... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.2.6      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Private: Logging: Size limit (KB)'... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.2.7      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Private: Logging: Log dropped pack... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.2.8      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Private: Logging: Log successful c... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.3.1      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Public: Firewall state' is set to ... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.3.2      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Public: Inbound connections' is se... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.3.3      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Public: Outbound connections' is s... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.3.4      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Public: Settings: Display a notifi... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.3.5      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Public: Settings: Apply local fire... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.3.6      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Public: Settings: Apply local conn... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.3.7      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Public: Logging: Name' is set to '... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.3.8      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Public: Logging: Size limit (KB)' ... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.3.9      L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Public: Logging: Log dropped packe... Group Policy Settings     True        
9.3.10     L1    Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Public: Logging: Log successful co... Group Policy Settings     True        
17.1.1     L1    Ensure 'Audit Credential Validation' is set to 'Success and ... Group Policy Settings     True        
17.1.2     L1    Ensure 'Audit Kerberos Authentication Service' is set to 'Su... Group Policy Settings     True        
17.1.3     L1    Ensure 'Audit Kerberos Service Ticket Operations' is set to ... Group Policy Settings     True        
17.2.1     L1    Ensure 'Audit Application Group Management' is set to 'Succe... Group Policy Settings     True        
17.2.2     L1    Ensure 'Audit Computer Account Management' is set to include... Group Policy Settings     True        
17.2.3     L1    Ensure 'Audit Distribution Group Management' is set to inclu... Group Policy Settings     True        
17.2.4     L1    Ensure 'Audit Other Account Management Events' is set to inc... Group Policy Settings     True        
17.2.5     L1    Ensure 'Audit Security Group Management' is set to include '... Group Policy Settings     True        
17.2.6     L1    Ensure 'Audit User Account Management' is set to 'Success an... Group Policy Settings     True        
17.3.1     L1    Ensure 'Audit PNP Activity' is set to include 'Success'         Group Policy Settings     True        
17.3.2     L1    Ensure 'Audit Process Creation' is set to include 'Success'     Group Policy Settings     True        
17.4.1     L1    Ensure 'Audit Directory Service Access' is set to include 'F... Group Policy Settings     True        
17.4.2     L1    Ensure 'Audit Directory Service Changes' is set to include '... Group Policy Settings     True        
17.5.1     L1    Ensure 'Audit Account Lockout' is set to include 'Failure'      Group Policy Settings     True        
17.5.2     L1    Ensure 'Audit Group Membership' is set to include 'Success'     Group Policy Settings     True        
17.5.3     L1    Ensure 'Audit Logoff' is set to include 'Success'               Group Policy Settings     True        
17.5.4     L1    Ensure 'Audit Logon' is set to 'Success and Failure'            Group Policy Settings     True        
17.5.5     L1    Ensure 'Audit Other Logon/Logoff Events' is set to 'Success ... Group Policy Settings     True        
17.5.6     L1    Ensure 'Audit Special Logon' is set to include 'Success'        Group Policy Settings     True        
17.6.1     L1    Ensure 'Audit Detailed File Share' is set to include 'Failure'  Group Policy Settings     True        
17.6.2     L1    Ensure 'Audit File Share' is set to 'Success and Failure'       Group Policy Settings     True        
17.6.3     L1    Ensure 'Audit Other Object Access Events' is set to 'Success... Group Policy Settings     True        
17.6.4     L1    Ensure 'Audit Removable Storage' is set to 'Success and Fail... Group Policy Settings     True        
17.7.1     L1    Ensure 'Audit Audit Policy Change' is set to include 'Success'  Group Policy Settings     True        
17.7.2     L1    Ensure 'Audit Authentication Policy Change' is set to includ... Group Policy Settings     True        
17.7.3     L1    Ensure 'Audit Authorization Policy Change' is set to include... Group Policy Settings     True        
17.7.4     L1    Ensure 'Audit MPSSVC Rule-Level Policy Change' is set to 'Su... Group Policy Settings     True        
17.7.5     L1    Ensure 'Audit Other Policy Change Events' is set to include ... Group Policy Settings     True        
17.8.1     L1    Ensure 'Audit Sensitive Privilege Use' is set to 'Success an... Group Policy Settings     True        
17.9.1     L1    Ensure 'Audit IPsec Driver' is set to 'Success and Failure'     Group Policy Settings     True        
17.9.2     L1    Ensure 'Audit Other System Events' is set to 'Success and Fa... Group Policy Settings     True        
17.9.3     L1    Ensure 'Audit Security State Change' is set to include 'Succ... Group Policy Settings     True        
17.9.4     L1    Ensure 'Audit Security System Extension' is set to include '... Group Policy Settings     True        
17.9.5     L1    Ensure 'Audit System Integrity' is set to 'Success and Failure' Group Policy Settings     True        
18.1.1.1   L1    Ensure 'Prevent enabling lock screen camera' is set to 'Enab... Group Policy Settings     True        
18.1.1.2   L1    Ensure 'Prevent enabling lock screen slide show' is set to '... Group Policy Settings     True        
18.1.2.2   L1    Ensure 'Allow users to enable online speech recognition serv... Group Policy Settings     True        