
RecommendationNumber  RecommendationName                                                                                  Source                    Pass    
--------------------  ------------------                                                                                  ------                    ----    
1.1.1                 (L1) Ensure 'Enforce password history' is set to '24 or more password(s)'                           Group Policy Settings     True    
1.1.2                 (L1) Ensure 'Maximum password age' is set to '365 or fewer days, but not 0'                         Group Policy Settings     True    
1.1.3                 (L1) Ensure 'Minimum password age' is set to '1 or more day(s)'                                     Group Policy Settings     True    
1.1.4                 (L1) Ensure 'Minimum password length' is set to '14 or more character(s)'                           Group Policy Settings     True    
1.1.5                 (L1) Ensure 'Password must meet complexity requirements' is set to 'Enabled'                        Group Policy Settings     True    
1.1.7                 (L1) Ensure 'Store passwords using reversible encryption' is set to 'Disabled'                      Group Policy Settings     True    
1.2.1                 (L1) Ensure 'Account lockout duration' is set to '15 or more minute(s)'                             Group Policy Settings     True    
1.2.2                 (L1) Ensure 'Account lockout threshold' is set to '5 or fewer invalid logon attempt(s), but not 0'  Group Policy Settings     True    
1.2.2                 (L1) Ensure 'Reset account lockout counter after' is set to '15 or more minute(s)'                  Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.1                 (L1) Ensure 'Access Credential Manager as a trusted caller' is set to 'No One'                      Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.2                 (L1) Ensure 'Access this computer from the network' is set to 'Administrators, Authenticated Use... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.4                 (L1) Ensure 'Act as part of the operating system' is set to 'No One'                                Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.5                 (L1) Ensure 'Add workstations to domain' is set to 'Administrators' (DC only)                       Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.6                 (L1) Ensure 'Adjust memory quotas for a process' is set to 'Administrators, LOCAL SERVICE, NETWO... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.6                 (L1) Ensure 'Adjust memory quotas for a process' is set to 'Administrators, LOCAL SERVICE, NETWO... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.7                 (L1) Ensure 'Allow log on locally' is set to 'Administrators'                                       Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.8                 (L1) Ensure 'Allow log on through Remote Desktop Services' is set to 'Administrators' (DC only)     Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.7                 (L1) Ensure 'Allow log on locally' is set to 'Administrators'                                       Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.11                (L1) Ensure 'Change the system time' is set to 'Administrators, LOCAL SERVICE'                      Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.12                (L1) Ensure 'Change the time zone' is set to 'Administrators, LOCAL SERVICE'                        Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.13                (L1) Ensure 'Create a pagefile' is set to 'Administrators'                                          Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.14                (L1) Ensure 'Create a token object' is set to 'No One'                                              Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.15                (L1) Ensure 'Create global objects' is set to 'Administrators, LOCAL SERVICE, NETWORK SERVICE, S... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.16                (L1) Ensure 'Create permanent shared objects' is set to 'No One'                                    Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.17                (L1) Ensure 'Create symbolic links' is set to 'Administrators' (DC only)                            Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.19                (L1) Ensure 'Debug programs' is set to 'Administrators'                                             Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.20                (L1) Ensure 'Deny access to this computer from the network' to include 'Guests' (DC only)           Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.22                (L1) Ensure 'Deny log on as a batch job' to include 'Guests'                                        Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.23                (L1) Ensure 'Deny log on as a service' to include 'Guests'                                          Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.24                (L1) Ensure 'Deny log on locally' to include 'Guests'                                               Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.25                (L1) Ensure 'Deny log on through Remote Desktop Services' to include 'Guests' (DC only)             Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.27                (L1) Ensure 'Enable computer and user accounts to be trusted for delegation' is set to 'Administ... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.29                (L1) Ensure 'Force shutdown from a remote system' is set to 'Administrators'                        Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.30                (L1) Ensure 'Generate security audits' is set to 'LOCAL SERVICE, NETWORK SERVICE'                   Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.31                (L1) Ensure 'Impersonate a client after authentication' is set to 'Administrators, LOCAL SERVICE... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.33                (L1) Ensure 'Increase scheduling priority' is set to 'Administrators, Window Manager\Window Mana... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.34                (L1) Ensure 'Load and unload device drivers' is set to 'Administrators'                             Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.35                (L1) Ensure 'Lock pages in memory' is set to 'No One'                                               Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.36                (L2) Ensure 'Log on as a batch job' is set to 'Administrators' (DC Only)                            Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.37                (L1) Ensure 'Manage auditing and security log' is set to 'Administrators' and (when Exchange is ... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.39                (L1) Ensure 'Modify an object label' is set to 'No One'                                             Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.40                (L1) Ensure 'Modify firmware environment values' is set to 'Administrators'                         Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.41                (L1) Ensure 'Perform volume maintenance tasks' is set to 'Administrators'                           Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.42                (L1) Ensure 'Profile single process' is set to 'Administrators'                                     Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.43                (L1) Ensure 'Profile system performance' is set to 'Administrators, NT SERVICE\WdiServiceHost'      Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.44                (L1) Ensure 'Replace a process level token' is set to 'LOCAL SERVICE, NETWORK SERVICE'              Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.45                (L1) Ensure 'Restore files and directories' is set to 'Administrators'                              Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.46                (L1) Ensure 'Shut down the system' is set to 'Administrators'                                       Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.47                (L1) Ensure 'Synchronize directory service data' is set to 'No One' (DC only)                       Group Policy Settings     True    
2.2.48                (L1) Ensure 'Take ownership of files or other objects' is set to 'Administrators'                   Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.1.1               (L1) Ensure 'Accounts: Block Microsoft accounts' is set to 'Users can't add or log on with Micro... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.1.3               (L1) Ensure 'Accounts: Limit local account use of blank passwords to console logon only' is set ... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.1.4               (L1) Configure 'Accounts: Rename administrator account'                                             Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.1.5               (L1) Configure 'Accounts: Rename guest account'                                                     Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.2.1               (L1) Ensure 'Audit: Force audit policy subcategory settings (Windows Vista or later) to override... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.2.2               (L1) Ensure 'Audit: Shut down system immediately if unable to log security audits' is set to 'Di... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.4.1               (L1) Ensure 'Devices: Allowed to format and eject removable media' is set to 'Administrators'       Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.4.2               (L1) Ensure 'Devices: Prevent users from installing printer drivers' is set to 'Enabled'            Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.5.1               (L1) Ensure 'Domain controller: Allow server operators to schedule tasks' is set to 'Disabled' (... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.5.2               (L1) Ensure 'Domain controller: Allow vulnerable Netlogon secure channel connections' is set to ... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.5.3               (L1) Ensure 'Domain controller: LDAP server channel binding token requirements' is set to 'Always'  Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.5.4               (L1) Ensure 'Domain controller: LDAP server signing requirements' is set to 'Require signing' (D... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.5.5               (L1) Ensure 'Domain controller: Refuse machine account password changes' is set to 'Disabled' (D... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.6.1               (L1) Ensure 'Domain member: Digitally encrypt or sign secure channel data (always)' is set to 'E... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.6.2               (L1) Ensure 'Domain member: Digitally encrypt secure channel data (when possible)' is set to 'En... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.6.3               (L1) Ensure 'Domain member: Digitally sign secure channel data (when possible)' is set to 'Enabled' Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.6.4               (L1) Ensure 'Domain member: Disable machine account password changes' is set to 'Disabled'          Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.6.5               (L1) Ensure 'Domain member: Maximum machine account password age' is set to '30 or fewer days, b... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.6.6               (L1) Ensure 'Domain member: Require strong (Windows 2000 or later) session key' is set to 'Enabled' Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.7.1               (L1) Ensure 'Interactive logon: Do not require CTRL+ALT+DEL' is set to 'Disabled'                   Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.7.2               (L1) Ensure 'Interactive logon: Don't display last signed-in' is set to 'Enabled'                   Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.7.3               (L1) Ensure 'Interactive logon: Machine inactivity limit' is set to '900 or fewer second(s), but... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.7.4               (L1) Configure 'Interactive logon: Message text for users attempting to log on'                     Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.7.5               (L1) Configure 'Interactive logon: Message title for users attempting to log on'                    Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.7.7               (L1) Ensure 'Interactive logon: Prompt user to change password before expiration' is set to 'bet... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.7.9               (L1) Ensure 'Interactive logon: Smart card removal behavior' is set to 'Lock Workstation' or higher Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.8.1               (L1) Ensure 'Microsoft network client: Digitally sign communications (always)' is set to 'Enabled'  Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.8.2               (L1) Ensure 'Microsoft network client: Digitally sign communications (if server agrees)' is set ... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.8.3               (L1) Ensure 'Microsoft network client: Send unencrypted password to third-party SMB servers' is ... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.9.1               (L1) Ensure 'Microsoft network server: Amount of idle time required before suspending session' i... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.9.2               (L1) Ensure 'Microsoft network server: Digitally sign communications (always)' is set to 'Enabled'  Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.9.3               (L1) Ensure 'Microsoft network server: Digitally sign communications (if client agrees)' is set ... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.9.4               (L1) Ensure 'Microsoft network server: Disconnect clients when logon hours expire' is set to 'En... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.10.1              (L1) Ensure 'Network access: Allow anonymous SID/Name translation' is set to 'Disabled'             Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.10.4              (L2) Ensure 'Network access: Do not allow storage of passwords and credentials for network authe... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.10.5              (L1) Ensure 'Network access: Let Everyone permissions apply to anonymous users' is set to 'Disab... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.10.6              (L1) Configure 'Network access: Named Pipes that can be accessed anonymously' (DC only)             Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.10.8              (L1) Configure 'Network access: Remotely accessible registry paths' is configured                   Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.10.9              (L1) Configure 'Network access: Remotely accessible registry paths and sub-paths' is configured     Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.10.10             (L1) Ensure 'Network access: Restrict anonymous access to Named Pipes and Shares' is set to 'Ena... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.10.12             (L1) Ensure 'Network access: Shares that can be accessed anonymously' is set to 'None'              Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.10.13             (L1) Ensure 'Network access: Sharing and security model for local accounts' is set to 'Classic -... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.11.1              (L1) Ensure 'Network security: Allow Local System to use computer identity for NTLM' is set to '... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.11.2              (L1) Ensure 'Network security: Allow LocalSystem NULL session fallback' is set to 'Disabled'        Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.11.3              (L1) Ensure 'Network Security: Allow PKU2U authentication requests to this computer to use onlin... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.11.4              (L1) Ensure 'Network security: Configure encryption types allowed for Kerberos' is set to 'AES12... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.11.5              (L1) Ensure 'Network security: Do not store LAN Manager hash value on next password change' is s... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.11.6              (L1) Ensure 'Network security: Force logoff when logon hours expire' is set to 'Enabled'            Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.11.7              (L1) Ensure 'Network security: LAN Manager authentication level' is set to 'Send NTLMv2 response... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.11.8              (L1) Ensure 'Network security: LDAP client signing requirements' is set to 'Negotiate signing' o... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.11.9              (L1) Ensure 'Network security: Minimum session security for NTLM SSP based (including secure RPC... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.11.10             (L1) Ensure 'Network security: Minimum session security for NTLM SSP based (including secure RPC... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.13.1              (L1) Ensure 'Shutdown: Allow system to be shut down without having to log on' is set to 'Disabled'  Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.15.1              (L1) Ensure 'System objects: Require case insensitivity for non-Windows subsystems' is set to 'E... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.15.2              (L1) Ensure 'System objects: Strengthen default permissions of internal system objects (e.g. Sym... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.17.1              (L1) Ensure 'User Account Control: Admin Approval Mode for the Built-in Administrator account' i... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.17.2              (L1) Ensure 'User Account Control: Behavior of the elevation prompt for administrators in Admin ... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.17.3              (L1) Ensure 'User Account Control: Behavior of the elevation prompt for standard users' is set t... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.17.4              (L1) Ensure 'User Account Control: Detect application installations and prompt for elevation' is... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.17.5              (L1) Ensure 'User Account Control: Only elevate UIAccess applications that are installed in secu... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.17.6              (L1) Ensure 'User Account Control: Run all administrators in Admin Approval Mode' is set to 'Ena... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.17.7              (L1) Ensure 'User Account Control: Switch to the secure desktop when prompting for elevation' is... Group Policy Settings     True    
2.3.17.8              (L1) Ensure 'User Account Control: Virtualize file and registry write failures to per-user locat... Group Policy Settings     True    
5.1                   (L1) Ensure 'Print Spooler (Spooler)' is set to 'Disabled' (DC only)                                Group Policy Settings     True    
9.1.1                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Domain: Firewall state' is set to 'On (recommended)'                 Group Policy Settings     True    
9.1.2                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Domain: Inbound connections' is set to 'Block (default)'             Group Policy Settings     True    
9.1.3                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Domain: Outbound connections' is set to 'Allow (default)'            Group Policy Settings     True    
9.1.4                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Domain: Settings: Display a notification' is set to 'No'             Group Policy Settings     True    
9.1.5                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Domain: Logging: Name' is set to '%SystemRoot%\System32\logfiles\... Group Policy Settings     True    
9.1.6                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Domain: Logging: Size limit (KB)' is set to '16,384 KB or greater'   Group Policy Settings     True    
9.1.7                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Domain: Logging: Log dropped packets' is set to 'Yes'                Group Policy Settings     True    
9.1.8                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Domain: Logging: Log successful connections' is set to 'Yes'         Group Policy Settings     True    
9.2.1                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Private: Firewall state' is set to 'On (recommended)'                Group Policy Settings     True    
9.2.2                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Private: Inbound connections' is set to 'Block (default)'            Group Policy Settings     True    
9.2.3                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Private: Outbound connections' is set to 'Allow (default)'           Group Policy Settings     True    
9.2.4                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Private: Settings: Display a notification' is set to 'No'            Group Policy Settings     True    
9.2.5                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Private: Logging: Name' is set to '%SystemRoot%\System32\logfiles... Group Policy Settings     True    
9.2.6                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Private: Logging: Size limit (KB)' is set to '16,384 KB or greater'  Group Policy Settings     True    
9.2.7                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Private: Logging: Log dropped packets' is set to 'Yes'               Group Policy Settings     True    
9.2.8                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Private: Logging: Log successful connections' is set to 'Yes'        Group Policy Settings     True    
9.3.1                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Public: Firewall state' is set to 'On (recommended)'                 Group Policy Settings     True    
9.3.2                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Public: Inbound connections' is set to 'Block (default)'             Group Policy Settings     True    
9.3.3                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Public: Outbound connections' is set to 'Allow (default)'            Group Policy Settings     True    
9.3.4                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Public: Settings: Display a notification' is set to 'No'             Group Policy Settings     True    
9.3.5                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Public: Settings: Apply local firewall rules' is set to 'No'         Group Policy Settings     True    
9.3.6                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Public: Settings: Apply local firewall rules' is set to 'No'         Group Policy Settings     True    
9.3.7                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Public: Logging: Name' is set to '%SystemRoot%\System32\logfiles\... Group Policy Settings     True    
9.3.8                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Public: Logging: Size limit (KB)' is set to '16,384 KB or greater'   Group Policy Settings     True    
9.3.9                 (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Public: Logging: Log dropped packets' is set to 'Yes'                Group Policy Settings     True    
9.3.10                (L1) Ensure 'Windows Firewall: Public: Logging: Log successful connections' is set to 'Yes'         Group Policy Settings     True    
17.1.1                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Credential Validation' is set to 'Success and Failure'                           Group Policy Settings     True    
17.1.2                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Kerberos Authentication Service' is set to 'Success and Failure' (DC Only)       Group Policy Settings     True    
17.1.3                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Kerberos Service Ticket Operations' is set to 'Success and Failure' (DC Only)    Group Policy Settings     True    
17.2.1                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Application Group Management' is set to 'Success and Failure'                    Group Policy Settings     True    
17.2.2                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Computer Account Management' is set to include 'Success' (DC only)               Group Policy Settings     True    
17.2.3                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Distribution Group Management' is set to include 'Success' (DC only)             Group Policy Settings     True    
17.2.4                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Other Account Management Events' is set to include 'Success' (DC only)           Group Policy Settings     True    
17.2.5                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Security Group Management' is set to include 'Success'                           Group Policy Settings     True    
17.2.6                (L1) Ensure 'Audit User Account Management' is set to 'Success and Failure'                         Group Policy Settings     True    
17.3.1                (L1) Ensure 'Audit PNP Activity' is set to include 'Success'                                        Group Policy Settings     True    
17.3.2                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Process Creation' is set to include 'Success'                                    Group Policy Settings     True    
17.4.1                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Directory Service Access' is set to include 'Failure' (DC only)                  Group Policy Settings     True    
17.4.2                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Directory Service Changes' is set to include 'Success' (DC only)                 Group Policy Settings     True    
17.5.1                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Account Lockout' is set to include 'Failure'                                     Group Policy Settings     True    
17.5.2                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Group Membership' is set to include 'Success'                                    Group Policy Settings     True    
17.5.3                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Logoff' is set to include 'Success'                                              Group Policy Settings     True    
17.5.4                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Logon' is set to 'Success and Failure'                                           Group Policy Settings     True    
17.5.5                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Other Logon/Logoff Events' is set to 'Success and Failure'                       Group Policy Settings     True    
17.5.6                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Special Logon' is set to include 'Success'                                       Group Policy Settings     True    
17.6.1                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Detailed File Share' is set to include 'Failure'                                 Group Policy Settings     True    
17.6.2                (L1) Ensure 'Audit File Share' is set to 'Success and Failure'                                      Group Policy Settings     True    
17.6.3                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Other Object Access Events' is set to 'Success and Failure'                      Group Policy Settings     True    
17.6.4                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Removable Storage' is set to 'Success and Failure'                               Group Policy Settings     True    
17.7.1                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Audit Policy Change' is set to include 'Success'                                 Group Policy Settings     True    
17.7.2                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Authentication Policy Change' is set to include 'Success'                        Group Policy Settings     True    
17.7.3                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Authorization Policy Change' is set to include 'Success'                         Group Policy Settings     True    
17.7.4                (L1) Ensure 'Audit MPSSVC Rule-Level Policy Change' is set to 'Success and Failure'                 Group Policy Settings     True    
17.7.5                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Other Policy Change Events' is set to include 'Failure'                          Group Policy Settings     True    
17.8.1                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Sensitive Privilege Use' is set to 'Success and Failure'                         Group Policy Settings     True    
17.9.1                (L1) Ensure 'Audit IPsec Driver' is set to 'Success and Failure'                                    Group Policy Settings     True    
17.9.2                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Other System Events' is set to 'Success and Failure'                             Group Policy Settings     True    
17.9.3                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Security State Change' is set to include 'Success'                               Group Policy Settings     True    
17.9.4                (L1) Ensure 'Audit Security System Extension' is set to include 'Success'                           Group Policy Settings     True    
17.9.5                (L1) Ensure 'Audit System Integrity' is set to 'Success and Failure'                                Group Policy Settings     True    


